{
    "subject": "Fran\u00e7ois_Dupeyron",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "The_Officers'_Ward__film_",
    "human_readable": "Fran\u00e7ois Dupeyron created the film The Officer's Ward.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9057409167289734,
            "question": "What is the title of the film created by Fran\u00e7ois Dupeyron?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7966405749320984,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'The Officer's Ward'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7380642294883728,
            "question": "Is Fran\u00e7ois Dupeyron known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6615849137306213,
            "question": "Who were the actors involved in 'The Officer's Ward'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5603498816490173,
            "question": "Where was 'The Officer's Ward' filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5561586618423462,
            "question": "What impact did 'The Officer's Ward' have on cinema?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5138365626335144,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Fran\u00e7ois Dupeyron?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5131315588951111,
            "question": "What themes might be explored in 'The Officer's Ward'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43972060084342957,
            "question": "When was 'The Officer's Ward' likely released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40283581614494324,
            "question": "What genre might 'The Officer's Ward' belong to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fran\u00e7ois Dupeyron created the film The Officer's Ward.",
            "html": "yago_13691_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was 'The Officer's Ward' likely released?",
            "html": "yago_13691_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What themes might be explored in 'The Officer's Ward'?",
            "html": "yago_13691_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other films directed by Fran\u00e7ois Dupeyron?",
            "html": "yago_13691_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13691_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13691_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13691_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13691_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13691_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13691_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13691_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13691_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13691_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13691_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents clearly state that  Fran\u00e7ois Dupeyron directed the film \"The Officers' Ward\" (also referred to as \"La Chambre des Officiers\"). \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Fran\u00e7ois Dupeyron created the film The Officers' Ward. In several documents, it is mentioned that \"Fran\u00e7ois Dupeyron's distinguished The Officers' Ward (La Chambre des Officiers)\", and \"In a masterstroke of tension, Dupeyron makes sure that for 35 minutes after his injury, we don't get to see Adrien's face. It's a private hell that Dupeyron captures through point of view shots from Adrien's perspective...\", which implies that Dupeyron directed the film The Officers' Ward."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information provided clearly states that Fran\u00e7ois Dupeyron is the director of the film \"The Officers' Ward\" (La Chambre Des Officiers), which supports the triple stating that Fran\u00e7ois Dupeyron created the film \"The Officer's Ward.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}